{
    "subject": "resource/The_Last_Legion",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "The Last Legion is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.965514063835144,
            "question": "Is The Last Legion a movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8206617832183838,
            "question": "Who directed The Last Legion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8103820085525513,
            "question": "Can you name some films similar to The Last Legion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7822946310043335,
            "question": "What genre is The Last Legion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7560611963272095,
            "question": "What is the plot of The Last Legion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6520327925682068,
            "question": "Where was The Last Legion filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45410171151161194,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in The Last Legion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4503030776977539,
            "question": "What is the overall theme of The Last Legion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3379842936992645,
            "question": "Did The Last Legion receive critical acclaim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3271803855895996,
            "question": "What year was The Last Legion released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Last Legion is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8371_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did The Last Legion receive critical acclaim?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8371_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the overall theme of The Last Legion?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8371_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors in The Last Legion?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8371_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8371_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8371_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8371_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8371_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8371_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8371_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8371_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8371_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8371_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8371_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, I can evaluate whether the information supports the triple \"The Last Legion is a type of Film\".\n\nHere's the response in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple mentions that confirm \"The Last Legion\" is indeed a film, thus supporting the statement that it is a type of film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}